So let's practice using the configurations to see if we can influence the creativity of a model
So let's say for example, we take an entropic and we take a cloud 3/7a apply and we're going to say
Please write a story
About a robot learning how to cook and we say it's a short story
Okay, so we will maintain the maximum length to 600 something like this. This way. It's not too long and let's look at the randomness and diversity
So we know that a low temperature a low top P and a low top K
We'll really make a response a bit more
conservative so let's run this and see how it works
so here is
the story so there's
Kitchen there was a flurry activities as a chef and here is the story and
It looks interesting and it's
You know if we read the story probably it's very boring, you know
And if we are now trying to increase the temperature
We're going to get more creative output if we increase top P we're going to get more words that were maybe not cutting it in the first place
So we'll put it at maximum almost and
And in top K we're getting more words to choose from as well
So we'll give it a maximum of 500 so now we are going to ask the playground the the model to create a much more creative output
So let's do again
Please write a short story about a low robot learning how to cook
And now we are getting something very very creative
So there's like optical sensors and there's like an instructor that doing creps and and the robot is now
Eating and so on so this is a much more creative output if you want to compare these two
I'm going to include those into the code
directory so you can see a low
Low temperature prompt and high temperature prompts
But remember what all of these means so this is controlling the creativity of the model overall
Top P is controlling the percentile of words considered based on their probabilities and
Top K is how many words you want to be considered for choosing the next word
So hopefully this makes sense. Hopefully you saw
How these kind of configurations work and how the influence the model outputs so I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture